Michael Cuddihy Papers and Ironwood Press Records, 1932-2000 (bulk 1949-1988)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Chapbooks, 1972-1988
  - 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - I want to say listen, Tom Crawford.
    - None, river, Michael Burkard.
    - L'Après-midi d'un faune: le cygne d'autrefois, by Stéphane Mallarmé; with a translation, prelude and postlude by Hayden Carruth.
  - Piccione, Anothony, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Series V: Ironwood Press Office Files, 1972-1995
  This series contains the remaining files of the Ironwood Press. Very little routine office material was retained by Cuddihy, and most of the series is comprised of grant applications, reference requests for fellowships and Cuddihy’s letters of reference for other poets, and reviews of Ironwood.
  - Correspondence, incoming and outgoing, 1972-1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Copyright requests, 1979-1986 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Fellowship recommendations.(Restricted) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Editorial notes, [1972-1988] (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Subscriber lists, nodate (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1: Grants, 1976-1995
    - Arizona Commission on the Arts, 1984-1988 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines (CCLM), 1978-1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1976-1995 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Series VI: Publication Files relating to Michael Cuddihy, 1963-1998
  This is series is a record of Michael Cuddihy’s writing career. There are several poem collections, an alphabetical list of his poems and numerous drafts of his unpublished memoir.
  - Subseries 1: Poems, reviews, essays, articles and interviews
    - Collection of poems - Onlookers (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Collection of poems - Out of the ruins (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Collection of poems - A Walled garden (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous poems in a bound notebook (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Poems listed alphabetical A-M (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Poems listed alphabetical N-Y (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Poem fragments (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Reviews, essays, articles and interviews, 1870s-1980s (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Poems by other authors, 1970s-1980s (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2: Autobiography – working drafts and editors notes for Man on a Seesaw.
    - It ain’t no picnic, a polio survivor takes a second look, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Man on a seesaw, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Seesaw (incomplete), 1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Seesaw (incomplete), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Man on a Seesaw (posted notes), 1990s) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Man on a Seesaw - resume paper, 1990s (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Newer chapters: Lunch with Dr. Kissinger; Max Ascoli and The Reporter; The Sweetest life of all; The Running of the bulls; West, young man (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from editors and edit notes, 1970s-1990s (Box 27, Folder 2)